{
    "subject": "resource/David_Burtka",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "Actor",
    "human_readable": "David Burtka's occupation is Actor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.920897364616394,
            "question": "What are some of David Burtka's notable acting roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9173968434333801,
            "question": "Is David Burtka known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.905387818813324,
            "question": "What makes David Burtka a successful actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.903481125831604,
            "question": "Is acting David Burtka's primary career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8941426873207092,
            "question": "What is David Burtka's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8161910772323608,
            "question": "What role does David Burtka play in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7718521356582642,
            "question": "Has David Burtka acted in any movies or TV shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.711532711982727,
            "question": "Has David Burtka received any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5365630388259888,
            "question": "What type of performances is David Burtka known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37361258268356323,
            "question": "In what field does David Burtka work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Burtka's occupation is Actor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1920_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of performances is David Burtka known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1920_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has David Burtka received any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1920_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has David Burtka acted in any movies or TV shows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1920_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1920_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that David Burtka is an actor, and there are multiple statements confirming his acting career, such as \"David Burtka gained fame on Broadway.\" and \"He is known for his acting roles in theatre and television shows such as How I Met Your Mother...\" . Therefore, the value of the key \"output\" should be \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that David Burtka is an actor, and additional information indicates he also has other occupations such as a chef, singer, host, and magician. Therefore, the statement \"David Burtka's occupation is Actor\" is correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}